<idea-plugin>
  <id>com.warm-burnout.theme</id>
  <name>Warm Burnout</name>
  <version>1.2.0</version>
  <vendor url="https://github.com/felipefdl">Felipe Lima</vendor>
  <description><![CDATA[
    <p>The theme for developers who are already burned out but still have deadlines.</p>

    <p>Mostly warm palette, one cool type accent, contrast-audited to WCAG standards.
    Full UI theme: editor, sidebar, tabs, toolbar, popups, everything.</p>

    <ul>
      <li><b>Dark</b>: AAA contrast (7:1+) on every syntax token. For the 3am sessions.</li>
      <li><b>Light</b>: AA contrast (4.5:1+) on warm sepia cream. For when someone opens the blinds.</li>
    </ul>

    <p>Bold keywords, italic types, readable comments. The style system adds
    non-color cues for code structure when the warm palette starts to blur together.</p>
  ]]></description>
  <change-notes><![CDATA[
    <p>1.2.0: Classic non-Islands variants are back. Pick Warm Burnout Dark or Warm Burnout Light if Islands chrome causes performance or redraw issues for you (see IJPL-222923). Comprehensive per-language coverage for ~60 language plugins (Bash, Dart, Go, Haml, JS, Kotlin, Lua, PHP, Python, Rust, Ruby, Swift, TS, XML, YAML, etc.) so identifiers no longer fall through to teal/blue defaults. Compose composable function calls render in the function color. Semantic-highlighting and bracket rainbow palettes collapsed to five on-brand warm tones. Toolwindow stripe button hover and selected states have visible contrast against the panel. Tame bold TODO highlight, Rider/C# attribute coverage, Islands popup/tooltip backgrounds.</p>
    <p>1.0.2: Dropped classic variants. Islands themes only. Fixed toolbar borders and project gradient.</p>
    <p>1.0.1: Fix editor color scheme not loading when selecting the UI theme.</p>
    <p>1.0.0: Initial release.</p>
  ]]></change-notes>
  <idea-version since-build="242"/>
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
    <themeProvider id="com.warm-burnout.dark" path="/Warm Burnout Islands Dark.theme.json"/>
    <themeProvider id="com.warm-burnout.light" path="/Warm Burnout Islands Light.theme.json"/>
    <themeProvider id="com.warm-burnout.classic.dark" path="/Warm Burnout Dark.theme.json"/>
    <themeProvider id="com.warm-burnout.classic.light" path="/Warm Burnout Light.theme.json"/>
  </extensions>
</idea-plugin>
